>> Kyle Simpson: 如果您对 TypeScript 和 Flow 感兴趣，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you're curious
about TypeScript and Flow and
他们的不同之处，就是异同，但是
their differences, this is both
similarities and differences, but
尤其是不同之处，我觉得这篇文章很有帮助。
especially differences, I found this
particular article to be very helpful.
他们基本上都是通过两个项目
They went through essentially
both projects side by side,
所有不同特征的大长列表
big long list of all
the different characteristics and
它们的位置相同，相同，相同，以及它们不同的位置。
where they are the same, same, same, same,
and the places where they are different.
这篇文章很不错我建议你看看
It's a good article, so
I'd recommend checking it out.
总之，我要说的是 TypeScript 和流在
In summary, what I would say is that
TypeScript and flow are very useful in
很多人认为他们帮助解决他们的打字问题
that a lot of people are finding them to
be helpful to solve their typing issues,
更能让他们的类型变得更明显
helpful to make their types more obvious.
我觉得他们很沮丧或者只是我很沮丧
Where I find them to be frustrating or
maybe it's just me frustrated about
生态系统就是我们立刻跳的那是唯一的选择
the ecosystem is that we seem to jump
immediately to, that's the only option.
如果您具有类型，那么可以完全忽略类型并使用三重等号，或者
If you have types, you can either ignore
types entirely and use triple equals, or
你可以跳到另一个极端
you can jump to this other extreme,
在 JavaScript 的上面有一层层
which is layer on something
on top of JavaScript,
我认为这根本不是 JavaScript的 DNA
which I would argue is fundamentally
not really the DNA of JavaScript.
我希望两者之间能有一点关系
And I would like for
there to be something in between.